Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/rasulayadithya (LinkedIn) kiddie22.github.io/ (Personal) github.com/Kiddie22 (Portfolio)

Top Skills

Amazon Web Services (AWS)
Terraform
Cloud Computing

Languages

English (Native or Bilingual)
Sinhalese (Native or Bilingual)

Certifications

Advanced Java Programming
Postman Student Expert
Learning Java
Learn JavaScript Course
Java (Basic) Certificate

Rasula Yadithya

Associate Software Engineer at Surge Global Sri Lanka

Summary

A software engineering undergraduate with an interest in full-stack web development, cloud computing, and blockchain solutions. Prior experience in the industry creating and optimizing ERP solutions. Currently working as a full-stack developer focusing on MERN, Next.js, Nest.js, TypeScript.

Experience

Surge Global 7 months

Associate Software Engineer September 2023 - Present (1 month)

Software Engineering Intern March 2023 - August 2023 (6 months)

Informatics Institute of Technology (IIT Campus)
Undergraduate
January 2020 - June 2023 (3 years 6 months)

IFS

Software Engineer Intern July 2021 - August 2022 (1 year 2 months)

Arteculate

Digital Associate Intern June 2021 - June 2022 (1 year 1 month)

RichMUN

Secretary General - RichMUN 2020 January 2019 - January 2020 (1 year 1 month)

Galle, Southern, Sri Lanka

Secretary General at RichMUN 2020

Education

University of Westminster

Bachelor of Engineering - BE, Software Engineering · (January 2020 - June 2023)

Richmond College

· (2007 - 2019)